<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Cup of Tegan</title>
    <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Cup of Tegan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:28:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Freelance: A Retrospective</title>
      <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/freelance-a-retro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:28:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/freelance-a-retro/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I started got my first freelance frontend development project and I was a different person.
I have had a few opportunties to do freelance work over the last few years, but each time I have buckled under anxiety and the dread of not being good enough. Due to some other things that are happening in my life, this time I chose to stare those worries in the face and accept their challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY banana face mask</title>
      <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/banana-face-mask/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/banana-face-mask/</guid>
      <description>In general I don&amp;rsquo;t do routine.
My only routine is not having a routine.
So as you may expect, I don&amp;rsquo;t really have a beauty or skincare regime: I wash my face in the shower 🛀 and splash my face with soap 🧼 in the evenings sometimes if I feel like it. I don&amp;rsquo;t wear much makeup, especially not foundation but I am a terrible face toucher and skin picker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treat yourself like a Sim</title>
      <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/be-a-sim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/be-a-sim/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you have low days. Days that it is hard to get out of bed, let alone leave the house.
For me, these days are usually paired with pajamas and mild anxiety of what is outside my door, and the guilt of failing to be a &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; human being. It is the sort of day where I will just plunge into a computer game as it means I have to make very little in the way of real life decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero waste shops based in the UK</title>
      <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/2019-06-07-zero-waste-shops/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/2019-06-07-zero-waste-shops/</guid>
      <description> Groceries and home  Anything but plastic Zero waste club Plastic-free pantry  Clothing  Rapanui Huit denim  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 birthday wishlist</title>
      <link>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/2019-birthday-wishlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>https://cupoftegan.dev/blog/2019-birthday-wishlist/</guid>
      <description>Oh hey! It&amp;rsquo;s my 2️⃣7️⃣th birthday soon! 🎉
Gift ideas As most of you know, I am trying to reduce my waste. This adventure has been touching so many parts of my life and I have been trying to find a maintainable balance. It also means I am questioning the social constructs that have a habit of generating waste, and at this time of year, I am focussing on birthdays, specifically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>